there's no error but you're guessing
you see that commit snow error I'm glad
it translated
this way so God is saying Quran you
commit no error by
exactly
but it is
similar for God's command to the end
just to broadcast
they will not worshiping that it will
obey himself
practices right
that people have here that you know I
don't think of anything
yeah the only part is visiting the
prophets too that is that is
going to The Perfect Storm and speaking
to the prophets and all this is broken
foreign
this is
the normal times of Peace if you break
the state of something between
expired by offering the sacrifice those
who cannot afford the first leader is
doing hot and seven when they return
home last completing tests provided they
do not live at the sacred mosque now
this means the seven days when you go
back
but if you live well you're not going
perfectly
careful your son observed God the Lord
of God is good and possible
[Applause]
197 schedule that had this to be
observed remember I said on the eighth
day you have to be there
because there are specified today
had shall be observed during the
specified months thus whoever sets out
to observe had said obtained that
abstain from sexual intercourse even
being an arguments throughout cuts
so this is really self-control you
cannot say a word of cussing or anything
you don't say any bad words
I'm responding to you my Lord
whatever good you do God is fully aware
thereof
as you take Provisions for the journey
remember that the best provision is
righteousness
you shall observe me or you will possess
himself
thank you
okay any questions you had three
yeah
all in all this
is
two days of minute per day
minimum
and then on the ninth you must do
another problem
what about the other two days
it's coming up
these are coming up then
two or three
uh
just remember
yeah she's certainly trying to talk
Abraham out of sacrifice in the Sun
come on I'm gonna kill you son it
doesn't make sense
difference
foreign
and all the people must be there so we
have one million people
now they made it Easy by Building
Bridges so they are so asking two
stories of people
my parents couldn't do it so I didn't
but on their behalf
there's so much of a crowd
you're a certain age
so I collected let me see seven for
myself seven for my father seven to my
mother and there was another sick person
to pretended it was on here
one at a time
foreign let's go
if you have somebody you don't like it's
bigger
because nobody sees however
[Laughter]
aim at his head
[Music]
as funny as some people get carried away
in that direction because
their diet is turning them just think of
that
that's it
and you are throwing stones that says
get carried away and they throw out
their shoes
on that thing yeah
foreign
or not to say that God ordered Abraham
to himself
out of sacrificing himself
Abraham thinks Abraham thinks God orders
him because that's why the son and
Abraham was going
uh on that assumption that God that is
obeying God
so the idea is to disobey God because
Abraham was convinced that God wants him
to to kill his son of course this the
whole thing is God's word it's the best
but the fact is God would love to order
himself
and obviously does not want him to put
his son for God intervene and said this
thanks to our professor again
so the two days the minute that will
come up in two or three
you'll be thrown in Satan yeah
but
the seventh heaven seven seven universes
seven Gates of Hell
I don't know
our see this our world consists of seven
universities
the Hereafter is the earth and the
verses
the Earth being held
the hardest in God
198.
thank you
you commit no sin by seeking commercial
benefits during hearts
when you find okay now we're gonna stop
at this Center
just say yeah you're going to take
advantage of being very hard
by wholesale a bunch of purple
to bring them here as a faith and you
set them
to the Muslims there is perfume from
us
and you make a lot of money
so that's what this person said you
commit no sin by sending commercial
benefits will have
when you fired from about that's on the
evening
of the ninth day do you think you have
to remember that God at the sacred
Shrine of Muslim
this is where you collect the stone
we're driving
you prayed you prayed the memory balance
[Music]
and you collect
49 storms okay seven seven five seven
gravity what they do in Saudi Arabia
they go the clocks go to the places
where they stand to absorb they collect
them and go back to Missouri
yeah and then the people collect them
authorities they collect them again
thank you
commemorate God for guiding you because
of the guidance you are really straight
199.
one night tonight we shall fight
together with the rest of the people and
seek God's forgiveness God Is Forgiven
merciful now fighting from our part or
being on our apart
it should remind you of the day of dirty
the people are equal there's no Rich no
poor
and it's a wrong a great number of
people one million people from the Hills
the day of judgment to be like this all
past present Pearson Generations will be
up for the same time on this Earth
it's gonna be very crowded
positive
Supply forever because there's no
distinction that there's no detention to
read some food
they will not preserve a special place
in the hereafter
for Ronald Reagan
well this is the presidential suite
yeah
exactly oh yeah
200 once you complete your duties of
worship we shall continue to remember
God just as you remember your own
parents or even better
some people may say our Lord give us in
this life in while they have no share in
the Iraq
others would say our Lord let us be
righteous in this life and righteous of
the Hereafter and spill us the agony of
help
each of these will read the books of
their word God and God is most efficient
attractive
like like I said some people spend the
life here seeking the materials of this
world concerned about the blink of an
hour and protecting the eternal life
now 203 are the final two days you've
had two or three
you shall commemorate God during the
specified day
after that
two to three days of minutes
thus if you complete this in two days
you commit no error and if you stay
longer you commit no error so now as you
maintain righteousness you see here the
openness
because sometimes it's impossible for
you to leave
when you want to there's so many people
and only a few bosses
able to live
and show them
perfectly all right because when God
says
four steps then that's it fourth step
but when he says it's okay to those
mindset and it is okay mindset but it
doesn't know the Quran is very careful
and takes all all circumstances into
consideration
which had observe God and know that you
will be gathered before him
what does it have
okay
we're looking for him to stop
sorry yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
look at it
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
among the people one may impressed
before he is
going to property
miserable
then there are those who readily devote
themselves to attain God's presence
dress display
s
are they waiting until God himself comes
to them
this happens
foreign
thank you
very much foreign
foreign
Commandments
or World Series when you're doing it the
right way and someone tells you you're
supposed to do more yeah I bet that
happened in there
and they're so righteous you know when
you're not doing it completely right you
don't want to add more
okay
no I think there was no business for
example as a submission for that you
would have subscribe that's what God
says there's nothing to do
and you know that's not the question of
pressing because God says you request to
specifies what can you do
you just
strictly adhere to what God is saying
you don't live here because Satan wants
you to be here God wants you to do
something else
instead of four
you know
she had problems yes of Satan as he's
walking along
they always adds more steps to
everything more prayer more than we do
more of this more that and it's playing
like a double meaning and with Special
Steps
you know you could you could blindly put
on statements in Egypt open you know
typically like this and work all those
extra steps
the idea is to make yeah
operations
I've been waiting until God himself
together
for them they walked across the Red Sea
walk no Bridge
there's no Bridge
walk across the Red Sea and then pharaoh
and his army followed and the water
closes right before their eyes
and they still wanted to worship the cat
and so this is these are the questions
and we are the same people
Murphy's
we saw that the Quran is from God you
know what more what more can you do
prove to let me just come down
but some people are not satisfied they
would like to they would like a life
exactly
request because it seems that uh
certainly 210
is connected with 211 it is the first
because as We Know
the Jews have asked Moses
who is he what's his name you want to
see me
you want to see Allah
and yet
they were given so many things so many
favors from Allah and they were not
satisfied
and now as you say
there are so many things in the Quran
and
that's the question gratitude I think
ungratefulness
well
she references
a big
woman he told Jewish
that's probably okay
not really
set too much
yeah
someone told him about that guy coming
to the world and the light of the Lord
the most
part
you said something like that dude
thank you
but what about mentioning holding the
seven universes
um
however the righteous will rank high
above them in the day of Resurrection
without clothes
the people used to be one who wanted
and since we're going to scripture is
extract this book
ironically if those received this
scripture involved
that this good among themselves I can
serious judgment for one another
distribution according to the skills
like that
um
verse 2 12 you know
music or describe some people saying you
know you only have one life to live
you think that is the only right and
it's the greatest life before you know
so they live with us and you know do
whatever you think so
okay
but uh
uh
well you know
these people
the reward is there
it's a matter of time but what is time
has to be actually a degree though
it was interested because
foreign
[Music]
tonight